(Sheldon:)You stayed in Michigan all week
to avoid being around me?
(Amy:)No, no, not just that.
(Penny:)I mean...
(Amy:)Detroit is beautiful
when it's sleeting.
(Sheldon:)You know, I'm not the only one
(Sheldon:)who's unpleasant
when they're sick.
(Sheldon:)When Penny got food poisoning,
she threw up so loudly
(Sheldon:)I could barely hear
the television.
(Amy:)Ooh, I just heard something.
(Amy:)Might be hail, might be gunfire.
(Amy:)Either way, I'm gonna go
take pictures. Bye.
(Raj:)Hey, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Hey. Where's Sheldon?
(Stuart:)Still sick?
LEONARD: No, he's fine.
(Leonard:)We just needed
a little break.
(Stuart:)Yeah, I get that.
(Stuart:)When I brought him his comics
the other day,
he said, “Oh, great,
Death is literally at my door.”
(Howard:)He was being a jerk
to everyone.
(Howard:)Don't take it personally.
(Stuart:)Oh, I'm on so many
antidepressants,
(Stuart:)I couldn't if I wanted to.
(Raj:)I wish we could do more stuff
without Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I wish that all the time.
(Leonard:)Usually before I blow
out birthday candles.